{"animal":[{"level":"1","type":"animal","question":"I meow and love to play with string. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥛 I like to drink milk."},{"text":"🧶 I chase mice."},{"text":"🐈 I have soft fur."}],"options":[{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Cat","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bird","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"2","type":"animal","question":"I say \"woof\" and wag my tail. I love to play fetch. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦴 I like to chew on bones."},{"text":"🗣️ People call me man's best friend."},{"text":"🐕 I come in many shapes and sizes."}],"options":[{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Dog","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"3","type":"animal","question":"I quack and swim in the pond. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦆 I have webbed feet."},{"text":"🥚 I lay eggs."},{"text":"🧡 I am often yellow when I am young."}],"options":[{"label":"Duck","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Horse","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"4","type":"animal","question":"I oink and roll in the mud. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐷 I live on a farm."},{"text":"🐽 I have a curly tail."},{"text":"🥪 People eat me as bacon and ham."}],"options":[{"label":"Chicken","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Pig","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sheep","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"5","type":"animal","question":"I moo and give you milk. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐄 I eat grass in the field."},{"text":"⚫ I am often black and white."},{"text":"🍦 I help to make your ice cream."}],"options":[{"label":"Cow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Goat","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Donkey","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"6","type":"animal","question":"I have a long trunk and big ears. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐘 I live in Africa and Asia."},{"text":"🥜 I like to eat peanuts."},{"text":"🦣 My nose is very long."}],"options":[{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Elephant","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"7","type":"animal","question":"I roar and I'm the king of the jungle. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🦁 I have a big mane."},{"text":"🥩 I like to eat meat."},{"text":"👑 I am known for being brave and strong."}],"options":[{"label":"Tiger","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Lion","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Bear","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"8","type":"animal","question":"I hop and I love to eat carrots. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🥕 I have long ears."},{"text":"🐰 I live in a burrow."},{"text":"🐇 I like to hop around in gardens"}],"options":[{"label":"Squirrel","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rabbit","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Fox","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"9","type":"animal","question":"I swing from trees and love bananas. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐒 I live in the jungle."},{"text":"🍌 I like to eat fruit."},{"text":"🙊 I make silly noises."}],"options":[{"label":"Monkey","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Snake","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Turtle","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}},{"level":"10","type":"animal","question":"I hiss and slither on the ground. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🐍 I don't have legs."},{"text":"🦎 I shed my skin."},{"text":"🌿 I can be found in hot or warm places."}],"options":[{"label":"Snake","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Worm","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Alligator","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"animal","icon":"🐾"}}],"weather":[{"level":"1","type":"weather","question":"I fall from the sky, and help flowers grow. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💧 I'm wet."},{"text":"☔️ You need an umbrella when I fall."},{"text":"🌱 Plants need me to live."}],"options":[{"label":"Rain","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Snow","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Sunshine","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"☀️"}},{"level":"2","type":"weather","question":"I am yellow and warm, and I shine in the sky. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"😎 You need sunglasses when I'm out."},{"text":"🌞 I come out during the day."},{"text":"🔥 I make the Earth warm."}],"options":[{"label":"Moon","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Sun","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Stars","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"☀️"}},{"level":"3","type":"weather","question":"I am white and cold, and I fall from the sky in winter. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🧤 You can make snowballs with me."},{"text":"❄️ I'm made of ice."},{"text":"☃️ I cover the ground."}],"options":[{"label":"Hail","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Snow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Fog","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"☀️"}},{"level":"4","type":"weather","question":"I blow through the trees, and I can be gentle or strong. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🍃 I can make leaves move."},{"text":"🪁 You can fly a kite when I am around."},{"text":"🌬️ I'm air that is moving."}],"options":[{"label":"Wind","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Rain","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Fire","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"☀️"}},{"level":"5","type":"weather","question":"I'm a big, white thing in the sky. Sometimes I block the sun. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"☁️ I'm made of water droplets."},{"text":"🐑 I can look like fluffy sheep."},{"text":"🌧️ Rain can come from me."}],"options":[{"label":"Cloud","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Star","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rainbow","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"☀️"}},{"level":"6","type":"weather","question":"I come after the rain and have many colors. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🎨 I have red, orange, yellow, green, blue, indigo, and violet."},{"text":"🌈 I am curved."},{"text":"☀️ You need the sun and rain to see me."}],"options":[{"label":"Sunrise","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Rainbow","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Lightning","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"☀️"}},{"level":"7","type":"weather","question":"I am loud and bright, and I come with thunderstorms. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"⚡️ I am electricity."},{"text":"⛈️ I am often followed by thunder."},{"text":"💥 I light up the sky."}],"options":[{"label":"Fog","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Lightning","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Hail","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"☀️"}},{"level":"8","type":"weather","question":"I am frozen raindrops that fall from the sky. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🧊 I can hurt if I hit you."},{"text":"⚾ I can be small or big."},{"text":"🥶 I'm often found during thunderstorms."}],"options":[{"label":"Snow","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Hail","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Sleet","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"☀️"}},{"level":"9","type":"weather","question":"I am water vapor that you can't always see but makes the air feel heavy. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"💦 I am in the air around you."},{"text":"🥵 I make you sweat."},{"text":"🌡️ You feel me more when it's hot."}],"options":[{"label":"Humidity","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Wind","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Temperature","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"☀️"}},{"level":"10","type":"weather","question":"I'm a swirling storm with very strong winds and rain, that forms over warm ocean water. What am I?","hints":[{"text":"🌀 I have an 'eye' in the middle."},{"text":"🌊 I can cause big waves and flooding."},{"text":"🌪️ My winds spin around and around."}],"options":[{"label":"Tornado","isCorrect":false},{"label":"Hurricane","isCorrect":true},{"label":"Blizzard","isCorrect":false}],"additionalData":{"backgroundColor":"0xFF9370DB","category":"weather","icon":"☀️"}}]}